

Kristian Firedi

krisdifire.github.io kristianfiredi@gmail.com Tel: (+381)65/57-83-939 Addr: Djordja Servickog 20, Novi Sad, Serbia

I'm Kristian Firedi, a full-stack web and mobile developer with 4+ years of experience delivering commercial projects — from traditional web apps to Web3 solutions — using Next.js and Flutter.

I'm also an admirer of all things design and tech related, no matter the medium, with a strong passion for science and the ever-evolving inovations it inspires.

EDUCATION

Faculty of Philosophy, Novi Sad (SRB) (2018 -)

Masters degree in Romanian Language and Literature

Faculty of Philosophy, Novi Sad (SRB) (2014 - 2018)

(BA) Philologist, Romanian Language and Literature

University "1st December 1918", Alba Iulia (RO) (Feb - June 2018)

Erasmus+ Student exchange program

West University in Timisoara (RO) (Feb - July 2017)

Erasmus+ Student exchange program

WORK EXPERIENCE

Flutter / Web Developer NS Web Development LLC	publishing it to the stores		
March 2021 -	Testing and debugging		
Present	Communicating and clarifying issues to other teams involved in the project in order to resolve or avoid said issues		
	Keeping track of multiple projects of varying scopes		

Project Management TalkBridge Ltd.	I and difficulty, and seeing them through to completion			
	Negotiating with suppliers concerning sales and deadlines			
August 2019 - March 2020	Finding solutions to issues that arise during project development and mitigating the same			
Visual Comprehist	Designing and writing lectures on multiple subjects for a			

Visual Generalist Embibe

November 2019 -February 2020 proprietary e-learning platform

Testing and bug reporting

Developing solutions and features for the platform

CERTIFICATIONS & AWARDS

(2023) Certified Smart Contract Auditor - Blockchain-council

(2022) First place in "Development for developers" team category - Broxus Hackathon

(2021) Dart and Flutter: The Complete Developer's Guilde - Udemy

(2018) Graduated top of my class - Faculty of Philosophy, Novi Sad

TECH STACK

NextJS

Flutter

Typescript

TailwindCSS

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

Solidity

TRAITS

Responsible

Resourceful

Open to new ideas

Quick learner

Creative

Calm under pressure

Enthusiastic

LANGUAGES

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	LISTENING	READING	SPOKEN INTERACTION	SPOKEN PRODUCTION	WRITING
SERBIAN	NATIVE				
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
ROMANIAN	C1	B2	B2	B2	B2
SPANISH	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1

Levels*:

A1 and A2 - Basic user

B1 and B2 - Independent user

C1 and C2 - Proficient user

*Common European Framework of Reference for Languages